Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage historical documents, 1950-1998; 9 linear ft. (7 boxes)
  - S.W. Arena History (Letters to Harry Weese from Zelda RE: Building) (Folder 27, Box 4)
  - Stage II Press Kit January 8, 1968 (Folder 28, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Dedication (The Evening Star) November 30, 1970 (Folder 29, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Dedication (New York Times) (Folder 30, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Dedication (Daily News) (Folder 31, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Theater (Folder 32, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Theater (Folder 33, Box 4)
  - Opening of Theater 1961 (Folder 34, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Dedication and Opening (Folder 35, Box 4)
  - Opening Night and Open Invitations 1965-1966 (Folder 36, Box 4)
  - Exterior Building Photographs (Folder 37, Box 4)
  - Kreeger Building (Folder 38, Box 4)
  - Spring Composite 1980-1981 (Folder 39, Box 4)
  - Brochure Photographs (Folder 1, Box 5)
  - Shakespearean Photographs (Folder 2, Box 5)
  - Old Arena Logo Slide (Folder 3, Box 5)
  - Brustein Photos and Hansberry Negative (Folder 4, Box 5)
  - Photographs of Bobby Short (Folder 5, Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets (Folder 6, Box 5)
  - Lobby Contacts (Folder 7, Box 5)
  - Lobby Contacts (Folder 8, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots, De Vincent (The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window) (Folder 9, Box 5)
  - Biography Material (Staff) (Folder 10, Box 5)
  - VIP Resumes, Bios, and Photos (Folder 11, Box 5)
  - H.E. Oliver Wright (British Ambassador) (Folder 12, Box 5)
  - Ronald Reagan Photo (Folder 13, Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives (Folder 14, Box 5)
  - VIPs and Playwrights Photos (Folder 15, Box 5)
  - VIPs and Playwrights Photos (Folder 16, Box 5)
  - VIPs and Playwrights Photos (Folder 17, Box 5)
  - Arena Stage Visitors (Folder 18, Box 5)
  - Guest Artists (Folder 19, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots (Negatives, Blow-ups) (Folder 20, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1972-1973 (Folder 21, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1972-1973 (Folder 22, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1974-1975 (Folder 23, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1974-1975 (Folder 24, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1975-1976 (Folder 25, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1975-1976 (Folder 26, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1976-1977 (Folder 27, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1976-1977 (Folder 28, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1977-1978 (Folder 29, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1978-1979 (Folder 30, Box 5)
  - Lobby Shots 1978-1979 (Folder 31, Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Photos 1970-1971 (Folder 32, Box 5)
  - Colorado College 1985 (Folder 33, Box 5)
  - George Abbott (Folder 1, Box 6)
  - Edward Albee (Folder 2, Box 6)
  - Robert Anderson (Folder 3, Box 6)
  - Charles Gordonye (Folder 4, Box 6)
  - Jean Anouilh (Folder 5, Box 6)
  - Sholem Ansky (Folder 6, Box 6)
  - Michael Frayan (Folder 7, Box 6)
  - Alan Ayckbourn (Folder 8, Box 6)
  - Anna Marie Barlow (Folder 9, Box 6)
  - Samuel Beckett (Folder 10, Box 6)
  - Brendan Behan (Folder 11, Box 6)
  - Daniel Berrigan (Folder 12, Box 6)
  - Restoration - Edward Bond (Folder 13, Box 6)
  - Michael Brady (Folder 14, Box 6)
  - Bertolt Brecht (1 of 2) (Folder 15, Box 6)
  - Bertolt Brecht (2 of 2) (Folder 16, Box 6)
  - John Mason Brown (Folder 17, Box 6)
  - Alexander Buzo (Folder 18, Box 6)
  - Truman Capote (Folder 19, Box 6)
  - Paddy Chayefsky (Folder 20, Box 6)
  - Anton Chekhov (Folder 21, Box 6)
  - Agatha Christie (Folder 22, Box 6)
  - Caryl Churchill (Folder 23, Box 6)
  - Noel Coward (Folder 24, Box 6)
  - Mart Crowley (Folder 25, Box 6)
  - Neil Cuthbert (Folder 26, Box 6)
  - Dostoevski (Folder 27, Box 6)
  - Friedrich Durrenmatt (Folder 28, Box 6)
  - Sherman Edwards (Folder 29, Box 6)
  - Christopher Durang (Playwright) (Folder 30, Box 6)
  - Lone Elder (Folder 31, Box 6)
  - T.S. Elliott (Folder 32, Box 6)
  - Jules Feiffer (Folder 33, Box 6)
  - Georges Feydeau (Folder 34, Box 6)
  - Dario Fo (Folder 35, Box 6)
  - Max Frisch (Folder 36, Box 6)
  - Athol Fugard (1 of 3) (Folder 37, Box 6)
  - Athol Fugard (2 of 3) (Folder 38, Box 6)
  - Athol Fugard (3 of 3) (Folder 39, Box 6)
  - Herb Gardner (Folder 40, Box 6)
  - Anthony Giardina (Folder 41, Box 6)
  - Jean Genet (Folder 42, Box 6)
  - William Gibson (Folder 43, Box 6)
  - William Gillette (Folder 44, Box 6)
  - Janusz Glowacki (Folder 45, Box 6)
  - Carlo Goldoni (Folder 46, Box 6)
  - Robert Ganshaw (Folder 47, Box 6)
  - Ron Whyte (Folder 1, Box 7)
  - August Wilson (Folder 2, Box 7)
  - Lanford Wilson (Folder 3, Box 7)
  - Virginia Woolf (Folder 4, Box 7)
  - Wendy Wasserstein (Folder 5, Box 7)
  - Anton Checkhov (Folder 6, Box 7)
  - Michael Weller (Folder 7, Box 7)
  - Norman Wexler (Folder 8, Box 7)
  - E.A. Whitehead (Folder 9, Box 7)
  - Tennessee Williams (Folder 10, Box 7)
  - Oscar Wilde (Folder 11, Box 7)
  - Thornton Wilder (Folder 12, Box 7)
  - August Strindberg (Folder 13, Box 7)
  - Brandon Thomas (Folder 14, Box 7)
  - Dylan Thomas (Folder 15, Box 7)
  - Henery David Thoreau (Folder 16, Box 7)
  - Peter Ustinov (Folder 17, Box 7)
  - Grants (Folder 18, Box 7)
  - Grants (Folder 19, Box 7)
  - Audience Surveys (Folder 20, Box 7)
  - Audience Surveys (Folder 21, Box 7)
  - Audience Response 1967 (Folder 22, Box 7)
  - Audience Response 1969-1970 (Folder 23, Box 7)
  - Audience Response (Folder 24, Box 7)
  - Audience Response (Folder 25, Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous Playwrights Photographs (Folder 26, Box 7)
  - Board of Trustees Retreat November 1970 (Folder 27, Box 7)
  - Audience Response 1970-1971 (Folder 28, Box 7)
  - Audience Response 1971-1972 (Folder 29, Box 7)
  - Theater as a Career (Folder 30, Box 7)
  - Regional Theater (Folder 31, Box 7)
  - The Cultural Climate (Folder 32, Box 7)
  - Performing Arts in Metropolitan Washington (Folder 33, Box 7)
  - Theatre Architecture (Folder 34, Box 7)
  - Theater as a Career (Miscellaneous Articles) (Folder 35, Box 7)
  - Institutional Review 1982-1983 (Folder 36, Box 7)
  - Institutional Review Packets 1982-1983 (Folder 37, Box 7)
  - Institutional Review Packets 1982-1983 (Folder 38, Box 7)
  - Subscription Plan (Folder 39, Box 7)
  - Newman Subscription Letters (Folder 40, Box 7)
  - News Release (Arena Stage Acting Company Gathers) (Folder 41, Box 7)
  - News Release (Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival) (Folder 42, Box 7)
  - Tech Department Critical Notice (Folder 43, Box 7)
  - Special Events (Folder 44, Box 7)
  - Photographs (Folder 45, Box 7)
  - Bibliography (Folder 46, Box 7)
  - Institutional Review Packets 1982-1983 (Folder 47, Box 7)
- Arena Stage financial documents and projects, 1980s-1990s; 20 linear ft. (27 boxes)
  Financial documents produced by the Arena Stage between 1950-2000. Includes documents on budgets, marketing, royalties, grants and donation information.
  - Arena Stage Associates - Year End Stats 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Direct Mail fundraisng/marketing stats, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - donor project / renewal letters 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    planning information for gaining new donors
  - NEA challenge Grant III 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 40th anniversary Budget, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 40th anniversary budget / 25th anniversary budget for the Living Stage (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Zelda's 40th Anniversary fund (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 40th annivesary gala table sales (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 40th anniversary gala prospectus (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 40th anniversary photo retrospective (Box 1, Folder 10)
    planning materials for retrospective
  - planned giving, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Development Report: Budget 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - financial statements; 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 40th anniversary general information (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1988 focus group report: subscriptions and multi-ticket buyers (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - marketing and ticket buying survey: 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - management meeting minutes: 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Arena Stage Associates: year end stats 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - preliminary proposal for annual fund 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - development calender, FY 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - communications 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Development Research Associate Computer Manual by Josh Milton (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - donor development research and stats mid 80's (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Black History Month at the Arena Stage (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - misc. financial forms (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - draft "Underwriters' Support" artical (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage graphics and logo (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - misc. charts, lists and financial reference information (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - sample thank you letters for donors (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - computer program information, notes (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - telemarketing information 1987-1988 season (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - phone/mail program report (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - telemarketing and mail marketing information (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - promo code report 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Institutional Development Counsel proposals (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - advertising spreadsheet (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Saturn / Columbia Books vouchers (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Asa and LS donor stats (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - campaign matrix information (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - fellows program information (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - London Tour 1988 - finances, contracts (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - London Tour 1988 - Correspondence/Press (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - London Tour - Final Deposits (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - London Arts Discovery tour information (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - London Tour 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National VIP ticket hotline information (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - LS Outreach Project 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - advertising budget plans, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - subscription budget calender, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - PR and Marketing budget info. 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - subscription campaign 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - subscription newsletter (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983, mailings and scheduels (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983: renewal invoice (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - subscriotions 1982-1983, brochure copy (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - subscriptons 1982: brochure copy (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - subscriptions 1982 renewal forms (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - subscription 1982-1983, minor printed materials (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - subcscription phone sales, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - subscriptions 1982, printing bids (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - subscription 1982, print ads (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - subscription calender 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "washingtonian" subscription 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - prospectus: Office for Advanced Drama Research (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - bicentennial celenrations, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - bicentennial celebrations general (you can figure the date out on your own) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - World Theater Festival, general info (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - World Theater Festival general (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - untitled (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Boston University Theater Renovation (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1967-1968 royalty information (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "The Foursome" Royalty payments (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - payment ot Bread and Puppet theater for performence (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Conflict of Interest" royalty payment (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - royalties 1974-1975 season (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - royalties 1975-1976 season (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - workshop production royalties (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - royalties 1976-1977 season (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - royalties 1977-1978 season (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Nightclub Cantana" royalty payments (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "Emigres" royalty payment (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - royalties 1978-1979 season (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - victor borge, royalty payments (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - " tiebele" royalty payments (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - royalty payment information, The Billy Bishop Company (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Loose Ends" royalty information (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "mummenschanz", royalty information (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - royalty information 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - royalty information 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Karamazov" production costs (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Karamozov" box office reports (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Banjo Dancing" production costs (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "American Buffalo" cost sheets (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Rosewater Extension" cost sheets (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "One Mo' Time" cost sheets and information (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Gertrude Stein" cost sheets (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Gertrude Stein", production costs (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "K2", production extension costs (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "Karamazov", production information (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "Avner the Eccentric", production information (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Tomfoolery", extension of performance info (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - royalty information ,1981-1982 season (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Banjo Dancing" production information/costs (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Animal Cracker" production extension information (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - royalty information, 1982-1983 season (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - "Banjo" production information (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - royalty information, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Karamozov" cost information 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Banjo dancing" cost information 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - royatly information, 1982-1983 season (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - royalty information, 1984-1985 season (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Foolsfire" royalty info (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Banjo Dancing" payments 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Raisin" royalty income 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Tintypes" Royalty income 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Tintypes" roaylty information 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "One Mo' Time" royalty income 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Tom Foolery" royalty income 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "K2" NYC royalty info 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "Anarchist" royalty income 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "Execution" royalty income 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "Ourselves Alone" royalty income 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cafritz Foundation Grant 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Cafritz Foundation 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cafritz Foundation 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Meyer Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Meyer Foundation 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Shubert Foundation Fiscal Report 1975 - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - United Arts Fund 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation grant, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Henderson will - $5,000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1975-1976 fund drive - Changes Explamation (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CBS Foundation 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Grant request - Queene Ferry Coonley Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bender Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Steel Foundation 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Philip L. Graham Fund Bicentennial Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - American Security and Trust Company $250,000 loan (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Grants 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Case history of the economic workings of Arena Stage (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation New Play Program (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - general (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1946-1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation grants, 1962-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NEA Challenge Grants 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Living Stage Grants 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - The Albacus Group (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Abbott Labratories contributions (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Abell Foundation (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Adams National Bank (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Aetna Life and Casualty (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - AKC fund (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - ALCOA Foundation (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Alexander and Alexander gift (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Alleco, Inc. Press info (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Alleco, Inc. correspondence (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Amax Foundation (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Amax, Inc. correspondence (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - American Broadcasting Co. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - American International Group (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - American Road and Transportation Builders (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - American Satellite (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - AMOCO Foundation (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - AMP Incorporated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Anheuser-Busch Companies, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Annenberg Foundation (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Anson Mills Foundation (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - ARCA Foundation (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - The Arcadia Foundation (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - ARMCO Foundation (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - The Arthur Foundation (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Arundel Asphalt Products, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - ASARCO Foundation (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Vincent Astor Foundation (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Bank of Delaware (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Barnes, Morris and Pardoe, Inc. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - T.A. Beach Inc. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Bill Labratories (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - W. Bell and Co., Inc. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Berger and Berman Builders, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Bernstein Family Foundation (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem Steel Corp. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - B.F. Saul Real Estate Investments Trust (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Black and Decker (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - BET Forum (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Black Student Fund (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Black Women's Community Foundation (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Black Construction Company (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Bodman Foundation (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Boker-Dick and Company (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Booth-Ferris Foundation (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Robert Bosch Corpotation (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Bowl America Inc. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Bradlees Department Stores (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lynale and Harry Bradley Foundation (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Braniff (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Briggs and Straton Corp. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - BWIA International foundation (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - The Brown Foundation Inc. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Brown Mechanical Inc. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Browning-Ferris Inc. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Brunswick Foundation (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Buck Trust (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Burger King (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Burlington Industries Foundation (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Burlington Northern (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Businessland Inc. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Bydale Foundation (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Boston Properties (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Boston Properties (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - CACI Inc. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Cambridge International (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Cameron Baird Foundation (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Camp Foundation, VA (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - capital Centre (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Mary Flagler Cary Chaitable Trust (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Chanel Inc. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Change for Good 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Champion International Foundation (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Chemical Bank (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Robert Sterling Clark Foundation (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Cointreau (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Columbia First Federal Savings and Loan (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Columbia Pictures (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Combustioneer (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Communication Through Art (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - The Community Resources Institute (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Commonwealth Land Title Insurance Co. (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Congressional Wives Club (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Cornelius-Calabrese Associates, LTD. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Arena Stage Associates (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Covington and Burling Foundation (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Crown Zellerbach Foundation (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Trammell Crow Company (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Trammell Crow Company (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Stone, Richard (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - O'Neil, Paul (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Olmer, Lionel (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Stoessel, Walter John, Sr. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Stweart, Patter (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Curry Foundation (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Crum and Foster Foundation (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Melrod, Leonard (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ourisman, John (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - O'Neill, Thomas P. Jr. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - O'Neil, Paul (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Muralock, David (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Ochsman, Ralph (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Munn, David W. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Arthur Cotton (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Quinn, Jack (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Preston, Jeanne Clark (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Preston, Barbara and John (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Phipps, Ogden (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Sandground, Mark (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Schwartz, Stewart (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Schattner, Dr. Robert (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - rolanali, Frederick and Mary (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Reynolds, Nancy Susan (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Shosteck, Herschel (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Silvert, Paula Robin (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Small, Albert (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Taylor, Charles (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Wilson, Kendall W. (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Young, William (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Wilkes, Charles Cafrity (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Slandig, Helen Ver (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Taubman, Alfred (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Tarlow, Sherwood (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Stoppard, Tom (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - expenditures tables: actual 1977-1978, budgeted 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - budgets estimated and actual 1971-1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Business Committee for the Arts (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cabaret survey by Guthrie (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Packaging Brokerage Business (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - production budget 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - production budget, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Bresler and Reiner (S.W. Construction) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - general correspondence 1 of 4 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - general correspondence 2 of 4 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - general correspondence 3 of 4 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - general correspondence (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Donor Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - board of trustees and intro to living stage (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Special Events (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Donor Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Donor correspondence and fundrasing info (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Donor correspondences and fundraising (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - stock certificates and deposit books circa 1956 (Box 21, Volume 1-2)
    Large box containing two 12 column books of stock/gift/donation information. Box also containes loose leaf stock certificates cira 1956, and stock books.
  - NEA grants 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - NEH - Arena Stage History grant (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - NEA - Director and Fellowship grant (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - NEA - Opera/Musical Theater grant "Rosewater" 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - NEA - Challenge grant application, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Commission for the Arts and Humanities, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Shubert foundation grant, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - the Shubert Foundation grant 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation grant,1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - COMSAT donation, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - the Cafritz foundation donation, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Exxon Corp. grant, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Public Welfare foundation donation, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation Report (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 1980-1981 potential funding sources (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "Uncle Vanya" production information, 1 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Uncle Vanya" production information, 2 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "Uncle Vanya", program proofs (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Uncle Vanya" Zelda Fichlander notes (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "Vior Dire" production information (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - "The Waiting Room" production information (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - "The Way of the World" production information (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - "What the Butler Saw" production information (Box 22, Folder 23)